Guide to the McKim Mead and White Architectural Records circa 1875-1950 PR 42
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Subseries II.A: 1950 Transfer
    - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, VA (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.349)
      General (172)
    - Washington Memorial Arch, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.350)
      General (52)
    - Washington Park Commission, Washington, D.C. (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.351)
      Mall (542)
    - Washington Park Commission, Washington, D.C. (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.352)
      Mall (560)
    - Wellington & Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.353)
      Offices, 120 Broadway (665)
    - Whitney, Payne, New York, NY (Box 1 of 7) (Offsite-box II.353)
      Residence (502)
    - Whitney, Payne, New York, NY (Box 2 of 7) (Offsite-box II.354)
      Residence (503)
    - Whitney, Payne, New York, NY (Box 3 of 7) (Offsite-box II.355)
      Residence (504)
    - Whitney, Payne, New York, NY (Box 4 of 7) (Offsite-box II.356)
      Residence (505)
    - Whitney, Payne, New York, NY (Box 5 of 7) (Offsite-box II.357)
      Residence (506)
    - Whitney, Payne, New York, NY (Box 6 of 7) (Offsite-box II.358)
      Residence (507)
    - Whitney, Payne, New York, NY (Box 7 of 7) (Offsite-box II.359)
      Residence (508)
    - Winthrop, Robert Dudley, Westbury, NY (Offsite-box II.360)
      Residence (215)
  - Subseries II.B: "Old Mixed Files"
    - Logan, General John A., Monument, Chicago, IL (Offsite-box II.361)
      Base for monument (33)
    - Cheney, Anne W., South Manchester, CT (Offsite-box II.361)
      Residence (34)
    - Players Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.361)
      General (38)
    - Selfridge, Admiral Thomas O., Mrs., Washington, D.C. (Offsite-box II.362)
      Residence (180)
    - Knickerbocker Trust Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.362)
      Bronx Branch (204)
    - Washington Memorial Arch, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.362)
      General and Sculpture for Pedestal (205)
    - Cuttings, Mrs. William D. (Offsite-box II.363)
      Monument, Greenwood Cemetery (208)
    - Architects Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.363)
    - Patterson, Robert Wilson, Washington, D.C. (Offsite-box II.363)
      Residence, 15 Dupont Circle (217)
    - Wyckoff, Peter B., Mrs., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.363)
      Residence (221)
    - Barney, Charles Tracy, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.363)
      Alterations to 67 Park Avenue (222)
    - Hotel Pennsylvania, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.364)
      Statler changes (223)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad (Offsite-box II.365)
      Pennsylvania Station, New York, NY (3)
    - Pope, Alfred Artmore, Farmington, CT (Offsite-box II.366)
      Residence (231); Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1899-1900 (231)
    - New York University, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.366)
      Dormitory, Retaining Wall, Fountain (235); General (24)
    - Strassburger R. Beaver, Gwynedd Valley, PA (Offsite-box II.367)
      General (264)
    - Racquet & Tennis Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.367)
      General (265)
    - Princeton University, Princeton, NJ (Offsite-box II.367)
      University Cottage Club (268)
    - Elliman, Douglas L., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.367)
      General (271)
    - Kellog, Howard, Buffalo, NY (Offsite-box II.367)
      Residence (272)
    - Metropolitan Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.367)
      Alterations (273)
    - Princeton Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.367)
      General (274)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad (Offsite-box II.368)
      Miscellaneous (275)
    - McKim, Mead, & White (Offsite-box II.368)
      General Works (276)
    - Freylinghuysen, Peter Hood B., Morristown, NJ (Offsite-box II.368)
      Alterations to Residence (277)
    - Lewisohn, Mrs. Frederick, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.369)
      Residence (278)
    - Newark Memorial Building, Newark, NJ (Offsite-box II.369)
      General (280)
    - Century Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.369)
      General and 1893 Re-Decoration (299)
    - State of New Jersey (Offsite-box II.369)
      State Capital, Trenton, NJ (300)
    - Moore, Edward C., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.369)
      Residence (301)
    - Ely, Mrs. Theodore Newel (Offsite-box II.369)
      Tombstone (302)
    - League for Political Education, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.369)
      Town Hall (303)
    - Racquet & Tennis Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.370)
      Old Building (304)
    - Bank of Buffalo, Buffalo, NY (Offsite-box II.370)
      General (305 1/2)
    - Wilgus, William J., Buffalo, NY (Offsite-box II.370)
      Tombstones, Forest Lawn Cemetery (317)
    - Lincoln Monument, Grant Park, Chicago (Offsite-box II.370)
      Seated Figure (318)
    - Lincoln Monument, London, England (Offsite-box II.370)
      General (319)
    - Music Hall, Youngstown, OH (Offsite-box II.370)
      General (320)
    - Washington Square Park, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.370)
      Flag Poles (322)
    - Aquarium, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.371)
      Addition (323)
    - Roberts, O.M.F., Avon, CT (Offsite-box II.371)
      Alterations to residence (324)
    - Benedict Memorial Music Pavilion, Providence, RI (Offsite-box II.371)
      General (326)
    - St Luke's Hospital, Duluth, MN (Offsite-box II.371)
      Additions and Alterations (327)
    - Yale University, New Haven, CT (Offsite-box II.372)
      Tablet (330)
    - Rogers, William A., Winter Park, FL (Offsite-box II.372)
      Residence (332)
    - Columbia Trust Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.372)
      Alterations of 1919 (333)
    - Wyandotte Hotel, Bethlehem, PA (Offsite-box II.372)
      General (334)
    - Butler, Joseph G., Jr., OH (Offsite-box II.372)
      Butler Institute of American Art, South Wing (336)
    - Shadyside Academy, Pittsburgh, PA (Offsite-box II.372)
      General (338)
    - Pan American Round Table Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.372)
      General (341)
    - Sloane, John, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.372)
      Residence (343)
    - L.C. Chase Company, Sanford, ME (Offsite-box II.372)
      Hotel (345)
    - Harvard Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.372)
      War Memorial (346)
    - Bowdoin College, Brunswick, ME (Offsite-box II.373)
      War Memorial (342)
    - Whitney, Alice K., Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.373)
      Residence (348)
    - Sloane, John, Residence, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.373)
      Alterations (349)
    - Choate, Mrs. Arthur Osgood, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.373)
      Residence (351)
    - St Peter's Church, Morristown, NJ (Offsite-box II.374)
      General (350)
    - St Paul's Church, Tivoli, NY (Offsite-box II.374)
      General (352)
    - Wuhu Hospital, Shanghai, China (Offsite-box II.374)
      General (354)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, NC (Offsite-box II.375)
      General (356)
    - Woodlawn Trust Company (Offsite-box II.376)
      General (357)
    - Gimbel Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.376)
      Alteration to store (358)
    - Bailey Park Country Club, Mt. Vernon, NY (Offsite-box II.376)
      General (359)
    - Smith College, Northampton, MA (Offsite-box II.376)
      Dormitories (361)
    - Chaloner, John Armstrong (Offsite-box II.376)
      Residence "Ravenswood" (362)
    - Flagpole, Cornwall-on-Hudson, NY (Offsite-box II.376)
      General (363)
    - United Savings Bank, Detroit, MI (Offsite-box II.376)
      General (377)
    - City of New York, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.376)
      Madison Avenue Widening (378)
    - Kew Gardens Apartments, Kew Gardens, NY (Offsite-box II.376)
      General (379)
    - Golf Courses (various locations) (Offsite-box II.376)
      General (380)
    - Barnes, James Residence, Princeton, NJ (Offsite-box II.376)
      Proposed Addition (381)
    - Markhoe, Mrs. James W. (Offsite-box II.376)
      Tombstone (382)
    - Martin, Luther, Washington Valley, NJ (Offsite-box II.377)
      Residence (383)
    - Sweet, Reginald L., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.377)
      Residence (386)
    - Adirondack Power & Light Corporation (Offsite-box II.377)
      Amsterdam Power House (387); General (388)
    - Hotel, Greenville, SC (Offsite-box II.377)
      General (410)
    - Commercial Building, Greenville, SC (Offsite-box II.377)
      General (411)
    - Scribner, Jr. Charles. A., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.377)
      Residence (413)
    - Barrett, E.F. Residence, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.378)
      Alterations (414)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, MA (Offsite-box II.378)
      General (415); Clock on University Hall (418); Fences, Gates, etc. (419); Tablets and Flagpole (420); Agassiz Panel (421); War Memorial (422)
    - Hotel X, 5th Ave. & 61st St, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.378)
      General (433)
    - Tammany Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.378)
      General (434)
    - Madison Square Garden, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.378)
      General (435)
    - Taylor, Joseph W., Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.378)
      Residence (436)
    - Taylor, Henry Augustus Colt (Offsite-box II.378)
      Sarcophagus, Woodlawn Cemetery (437)
    - Elliman, Douglas, L., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.378)
      Apartment Alterations (438)
    - Bacheller, Irving, Winter Park, FL (Offsite-box II.378)
      Residence (439)
    - Taft, Chief Justice, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.378)
      Residence (440)
    - Second Presbyterian Church, Lexington, KY (Offsite-box II.379)
      General (441)
    - Jeanne d'Arc Statue, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.379)
      Pedestal, Copy of statue in Rheims by Paul Dubois (442)
    - Oakwood Cemetery, Raleigh, NC (Offsite-box II.379)
      General (443)
    - Chapman Family, Bedford, NY (Offsite-box II.379)
      Memorials (444)
    - Eastman, George, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.379)
      Garden Pedestal (445)
    - Page, Mrs. Thomas Nelson, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.379)
      Memorial (447)
    - National City Bank, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.379)
      28th Street Branch (449)
    - Office Files (Offsite-box II.380)
      Stanford File (350)
    - Tiffany & Co., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.381)
      Buildings misc. (459)
    - North Carolina Department of State, Raleigh, NC (Offsite-box II.381)
      Agricultural Building (361)
    - Trinity Church, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.381)
      Phillip Brooks Monument (467)
    - Governor's Island, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.381)
      General (468)
    - Minneapolis Museum of Art, Minneapolis, MN (Offsite-box II.381)
      General (470)
    - National Life Insurance Company Building, Nashville, TN (Offsite-box II.382)
      General (471)
    - Morgan, J.P., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.382)
      Morgan Library, 1923 Alterations (472)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore Statue, Portland, OR (Offsite-box II.382)
      Pedestal (474)
    - Stillman, James A., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.382)
      Residence (475)
    - Steward, William R., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.382)
      Residence (476)
    - Woodcock, Frederick S., Buffalo, NY (Offsite-box II.382)
      Monument (477)
    - Church of the Ascension, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.382)
      General (478)
    - Butler, E.H., Buffalo, NY (Offsite-box II.383)
      Residence (479)
    - Federal National Bank, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.383)
      General (480)
    - Stillman, Anne, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.383)
      Apartment (481)
    - Guthrie, William Dameron, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.383)
      Townhouse (483)
    - Gorgas, William C. (Offsite-box II.383)
      Memorial (484)
    - Byrne, R.M., Montclair, NJ (Offsite-box II.383)
      Residence, Alterations (488)
    - Riverdale Country School, Riverdale-on-Hudson, NY (Offsite-box II.383)
    - Watriss, Frederick N., Roslyn, NY (Offsite-box II.383)
      Gravestone (493)
    - Hotel Bossert, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box II.383)
      General (494)
    - United States Army War College, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.383)
      Washington Barracks (512)
    - Washington Monument, Kansas City, MO (Offsite-box II.383)
      Pedestal (536)
    - Grand Hotel, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.383)
      General (537)
    - Rochester Gas & Electric Corporation, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.384)
      General (538)
    - Peabody College, Nashville, TN (Offsite-box II.384)
    - Rochester Savings Bank, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.385)
    - Eastman, George, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.385)
      General, 1902-1906 (543)
    - United States Military Academy, West Point, NY (Offsite-box II.386)
      General (544)
    - Munger, Robert Sylvester, Birmingham, AL (Offsite-box II.386)
      Tombstone (550)
    - McKim, C.F. Personal Files (Offsite-box II.387)
      Metropolitan Museum Trustee (558); Niagara Commission (559)
    - Edward C. Smith & Company, Philadelphia, PA (Offsite-box II.387)
      Bank and Office Building (562)
    - Church of the Paulist Fathers, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.387)
      General (566)
    - Whitney, Payne, Roslyn. NY (Offsite-box II.387)
      Residence (566)
    - 430 East 57th Street, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.388)
      Apartment Building (567)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, MA (Offsite-box II.388)
      Gates, etc. (568)
    - University of Rochester, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.389)
      Memorial Art Gallery (568)
    - 48 West 57th Street, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.389)
      Apartment Building (569)
    - Moulton, Arthur J., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.389)
      General (570)
    - Sherry, Louis, Narragansett, RI (Offsite-box II.389)
      Casino (571)
    - Bostwick, A.C., Mamaroneck, NY (Offsite-box II.390)
      Residence (571)
    - College of Physicians, Philadelphia, PA (Offsite-box II.390)
      Building (571)
    - Vanderbilt Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.390)
    - Choate, Arthur Osgood, Pleasantville, NY (Offsite-box II.390)
      Residence (589)
    - Cheney, Anne W., South Manchester, CT (Offsite-box II.390)
      Residence (594)
    - Cheney, Anne W., South Manchester, CT (Offsite-box II.391)
      Residence (596)
    - Babbott, Frank L. (Offsite-box II.391)
      Memorial, Greenwood Cemetery (598)
    - Macomb, Alexander Statue, Detroit, MI (Offsite-box II.391)
      General (598)
    - Monument, Sault St. Marie, MI (Offsite-box II.391)
    - White, Stanford Monument, St. James, NY (Offsite-box II.391)
    - Sherry, Louis (Offsite-box II.391)
      Mausoleum, Woodlawn Cemetery (598)
    - Wolcott, Henry (Offsite-box II.391)
      Monument, Woodlawn Cemetery (598)
    - de Alba (Offsite-box II.392)
      Ledger Tombstone, Trinity Cemetery (612)
    - Battery Park, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.392)
      Flagpole (613)
    - American War Memorial, Rome, Italy (Offsite-box II.392)
      General (614)
    - American War Memorial, Florence, Italy (Offsite-box II.392)
    - Skinner, Joseph A., Holyoke, MA (Offsite-box II.392)
      Tombstones (620)
    - Moore, Dr. Edward Mott, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.393)
      Monument in Genesee Valley Park (621)
    - Wadsworth, James W., Geneseo, NY (Offsite-box II.393)
      Louisa Travers Wadsworth Monument, Protestant Cemetery (622)
    - War Memorial, Newport, RI (Offsite-box II.393)
      General (623)
    - Martin, George F. (Offsite-box II.393)
      Memorial, Woodlawn Cemetery (624)
    - Dobbs Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.393)
      General (625)
    - Port Chester Park Commission, Portchester, NY (Offsite-box II.393)
      Tablet for Bush Homestead (626)
    - Chubb, Percy, Brookville, NY (Offsite-box II.393)
      Gravestones (627)
    - Holyoke Hospital, Holyoke, MA (Offsite-box II.393)
      General (628)
    - Morgan, J.P., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.394)
      Morgan Library (628)
    - Princeton University, Princeton, NJ (Offsite-box II.394)
      University Cottage Club (632)
    - Chanler, Marion and Winthrop, Geneseo, NY (Offsite-box II.395)
      Tombstones, Protestant Cemetery (639)
    - Governors Island, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.395)
      Barracks (640); Hospital (641)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad (Offsite-box II.396)
      Baltimore Station (641)
    - University of Illinois, Champaign, IL (Offsite-box II.396)
      General (641)
    - Thomas Jefferson Bust (Offsite-box II.396)
      General (642)
    - Mount Royal Club, Montreal, Canada (Offsite-box II.396)
    - Princeton University, Princeton, NJ (Offsite-box II.396)
      Fitz Randolph Gateway (642)
    - Woodward Statue, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box II.396)
    - Sherry, Louis, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.396)
      Restaurant and shop building (644)
    - Peddie School, Hightstown, NJ (Offsite-box II.397)
      Austen Colgate Hall (649); Field House (650); General (651); Guest House (652); Gymnasium (653); Wilson Hall Alterations (654)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Offsite-box II.398)
      General (673)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.398)
      Miscellaneous Notes, 1906 (675)
    - Miscellaneous N – Z (Offsite-box II.398)
      (687)
    - Fort Sumter, North Carolina (Offsite-box II.399)
      Memorial Flagpole to Major Robert Anderson (756)
    - Parounagian, Dr. M. B., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.399)
      Alterations to Residence, 126 East 39th Street (757)
    - Tilney, John S., Orange, NJ (Offsite-box II.399)
      Memorial in Rosedale Cemetery (759)
    - Mead, William Rutherford (Offsite-box II.399)
      Tombstone (785)
    - Columbia Yacht Club, New York, NYf (Offsite-box II.399)
      General (791)
    - City of New York, NY (Offsite-box II.399)
      West Side Highway Improvements (792)
    - City of New York, NY (Offsite-box II.399)
      East River Drive Improvements (796)
    - Brooklyn Institute, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.400)
      Reconstruction and Improvements (800, 801, 802)
  - Subseries II.C: 1968 Transfer
    - Academy of Medicine, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.401)
      General (1100); Correspondence with General Contractor, etc. (1108); Ventilation (1109)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 1 of 5) (Offsite-box II.402)
      Laboratories (17)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 2 of 5) (Offsite-box II.403)
      Laboratories, cont'd (17)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 3 of 5) (Offsite-box II.404)
      Chapin Hall (507)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 4 of 5) (Offsite-box II.405)
      Chapin Hall, cont'd (507)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 5 of 5) (Offsite-box II.406)
      Squash Court Building; Johnson Chapel Alterations; Power House; Alumni House; Hockey Rink; Hitchcock House (Octagon) (all 606)
    - Sleepy Hollow Country Club, Scarborough-on-Hudson, NY (Offsite-box II.406)
      General (606)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 1 of 10) (Offsite-box II.407)
      Theater (697)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 2 of 10) (Offsite-box II.408)
      Theater, cont'd (697)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 3 of 10) (Offsite-box II.409)
      Appleton Hall (28); General [no #]; Morgan Hall [no #]; Morgan Library (702); Genung House [no #]; Barrett Hall [no #]; Physics Bldg Alterations (945); Williston Hall [no #]; Observatory House (946); De Rose House (943)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 4 of 10) (Offsite-box II.410)
      Pratt Museum (708); Gymnasium and Natatorium (705); Infirmary (706); Little Red School (707); Houses (709)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 5 of 10) (Offsite-box II.411)
      Fletcher Memorial (935); Valentine Hall (936)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 6 of 10) (Offsite-box II.412)
      Valentine Hall (936)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 7 of 10) (Offsite-box II.413)
      Dormitories A and B (937)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 8 of 10) (Offsite-box II.414)
      Valentine Hall (936); Pratt Dormitory Alterations and Library (938); Inscription (939); Campus General Plan (940); Distribution System, Heating Electric, Water (941); Morrow Hall Alterations (942); Biology Building (948)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 9 of 10) (Offsite-box II.415)
      Merrill Place, Faculty Housing (947)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 10 of 10) (Offsite-box II.416)
      Allen Research Library (949)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge, Washington, DC (Box 1 of 7) (Offsite-box II.417)
      General (492)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge, Washington, DC (Box 2 of 7) (Offsite-box II.418)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge, Washington, DC (Box 3 of 7) (Offsite-box II.419)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge, Washington, DC (Box 4 of 7) (Offsite-box II.420)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge, Washington, DC (Box 5 of 7) (Offsite-box II.421)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge, Washington, DC (Box 6 of 7) (Offsite-box II.422)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge, Washington, DC (Box 7 of 7) (Offsite-box II.423)
    - White House, Washington D C (Offsite-box II.423)
      General (279)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.424)
      Pavilions C and ? (825); Laundry (826); Administrative Bldg. (827); Fences, Roadway, Gates, Balconies (828); Addition to Garage (829)
    - New York City Board of Education, Brooklyn, NY (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.425)
      Public School #4 (1031)
    - New York City Board of Education, Brooklyn, NY (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.426)
      Public School #4, cont'd (1031)
    - Colgate University, Hamilton, NY (Box 1 of 7) (Offsite-box II.427)
      General; Library; Proposed Science Building; Upper Class Residential Hall (all 545)
    - Colgate University, Hamilton, NY (Box 2 of 7) (Offsite-box II.428)
      Upper Class Residential Hall (545)
    - Colgate University, Hamilton, NY (Box 3 of 7) (Offsite-box II.429)
      Upper Class Residential Hall, cont'd (545)
    - Colgate University, Hamilton, NY (Box 4 of 7) (Offsite-box II.430)
      East and West Dormitories (546)
    - Colgate University, Hamilton, NY (Box 5 of 7) (Offsite-box II.431)
      East and West Dormitories; Eaton Hall Study; Campus Store (all 546)
    - Colgate University, Hamilton, NY (Box 6 of 7) (Offsite-box II.432)
      Extension to Gymnasium, Field House (547)
    - Colgate University, Hamilton, NY (Box 7 of 7) (Offsite-box II.433)
      Extension to Gymnasium, Field House, cont'd (547)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 1 of 15) (Offsite-box II.434)
      Project A (830)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 2 of 15) (Offsite-box II.435)
      Project A, cont'd (830); Project B (831)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 3 of 15) (Offsite-box II.436)
      Project A, cont'd (830); General (832)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 4 of 15) (Offsite-box II.437)
      General (832)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 5 of 15) (Offsite-box II.438)
      Project C (832)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 6 of 15) (Offsite-box II.439)
      Project C, cont'd (832)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 7 of 15) (Offsite-box II.440)
      Project D (832)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 8 of 15) (Offsite-box II.441)
      Project D, cont'd (832)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 9 of 15) (Offsite-box II.442)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 10 of 15) (Offsite-box II.443)
      Men's Dormitory (834)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 11 of 15) (Offsite-box II.444)
      Engineering Building (835)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 12 of 15) (Offsite-box II.445)
      Engineering Building, cont'd (835)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 13 of 15) (Offsite-box II.446)
      North Dorms (837)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 14 of 15) (Offsite-box II.447)
      North Dorms, cont'd (837)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT (Box 15 of 15) (Offsite-box II.448)
    - University of Delaware, Newark, DE (Offsite-box II.449)
      Residence Halls (1112)
    - Mary Fletcher Hospital & Nurses Home, Burlington, VT (Offsite-box II.450)
      General (836)